Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, student records
1850-2008
RU 262
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1096.67
(1068 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences.
Yale University. Graduate School
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 25-F (YRG 25-F), Student records of the Yale Graduate School.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Separated Materials
Several files were removed from various accessions for a project undertaken by the Registrar's office. Some folders were not returned to their original locations and were assigned a separate accession, 19ND-A-440.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Graduate Students; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Graduate School
- Student records [microfilm], circa 1847-1984; Accession 19ND-A-512
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
  - circa 1847-1966
    - Asronoff -Brown, F.B. (Reel 1)
    - Brown, F.M. -Bynum; Eggertsson -Godwin (Reel 2)
    - Roosevelt-Coan -Wanning (Reel 4)
    - Harris -Kennedy (Reel 5)
    - Kennelly -McManus (Reel 6)
    - McMaster -Opton (Reel 7)
    - Orbison -Russell (Reel 8)
    - Russett -Swift (Reel 9)
    - Swigar -Winser (Reel 10)
    - Winsor -Zytkowicz (Reel 11)
  - 1964-1969
    - Current students, Administrative Science - Philosophy (Reel 12)
    - Physics, Religious Studies, Language - Special registration (Reel 13)
    - Non-Ph.D. 1964-1968
      - Aamodt -Pincus (Reel 14)
      - Lang -Zvelich (Reel 15)
  - 1969-1970
    - Degree recipients and withdrawals
      - Abisch -Zuckerman (Reel 16)
    - Administrative Science -Microbiology (Reel 17)
    - Molecular Biophysics, Dept. of Special Registration, Students as of August 1970 (Reel 18)
  - 1971
    - Administrative Science (Bernard -Zola) -History of Art (Pospisil -Woodward) (Reel 19)
    - History of Science and Medicine (Boutellie -Whittaker) -MA MS MAT (Adams -Wood) (Reel 20)
    - DSR (Allen -Williams)-Grade cards for degrees conferred and withdrawls (Aarebot-Zukerman) (Reel 21)
  - 1972
    - Administrative Science -German (Reel 22)
    - History -Dept. of Special Registration (Reel 23)
    - Ph.D. degrees -Zannis (Reel 24)
  - 1973
    - Ph.D. (Albanese) -Withdrawals (Yoshida) (Reel 25)
    - Administrative Science (Anthony) -Linguistics (Williams) (Reel 26)
    - Mathematics (Barsum) -Statistics (Yadvish) (Box 27)
  - 1974
    - Abercrombie -Travis (Reel 28)
    - Administrative Science (Arnold) -History (Zarwan) (Reel 29)
    - History of Art (Anderson) -Statistics (Yadvish) (Reel 30)
  - 1974-1975
    - Ph.D.s conferred
      - Abrams -Economics (Litan) (Reel 31)
      - Economics II (Mansoor) -Psychology I (Kuhlman) (Reel 32)
      - Psychology II (Lamb) -Statistics (Wax) (Reel 33)
    - 1975
      - Graduate School -Woodbridge (Reel 34)
  - 1975-1976
    - Current students
      - Administrrative Science (Bassett) -History of Theatre (McCarthy) (Reel 35)
  - Student Grade Cards
    - 1976-1977
      - Administrative Science -Germanic Language and Literature (Reel 37)
      - History -Statistics (Reel 38)
      - Ph.D., December 1976 -Direct Special Registration (Reel 39)
    - 1977-1978
      - Degrees conferred -Division of Special Registration (Reel 40)
      - Current records -Italian (Reel 41)
      - Current Linguistics -Statistics (Reel 42)
    - 1978-1979
      - Abelove -Economics (Williams) (Reel 43)
      - Economic History (Eichengreen) -Renaissance Studies (Rico) (Reel 44)
      - Russian and Eastern European Studies (Caplan) -Statistics (Zelterman) (Reel 45)
    - 1979-1980
      - Alger -Engineering M-Z (Reel 46)
      - English A-L -Statistics (Reel 47)
    - 1980-1981
      - American Studies (Anderson) -Economics (Sillers) (Reel 48)
      - Economics (Simons) -Pharmacology (Wu) (Reel 49)
      - Physics (Ahmed) -Physiology (Yellen) (Reel 50)
  - Graduate School Transcripts
    - 1981-1982
      - History of Art -Operations Research (Reel 51)
      - Organizational Behavior -Ph.D. (Reel 52)
    - 1982-1983
      - Ph.D., December 1982 -May 1983; DSR -Astronomy (Reel 53)
      - Biology -English (Reel 54)
      - French -Spanish and Portuguese (Reel 55)
    - 1984 (May-December)
      - Allen -Zelterman; Afro-American -East Asian Studies (Reel 56)
      - English -Molecular Biology and Biophysics (also includes Economics and Engineering) (Reel 57)
      - Music -Statistics (Reel 58)
- Ph.D. and non-Ph.D. student records, 1973; Accession 1978-A-003
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2049
  Scope and Contents
  Includes Ph.D. files up to and including 1973 and non-Ph.D. files up to and including 1970.
  - Wils - Wimm (Box 342)
  - Wims - Witman, G. (Box 343)
  - Witman, He - Wolff, M. (Box 344)
  - Wolff, N. - Woodm (Box 345)
  - Woodr - Woy (Box 346)
  - Wr - Wu, H. (Box 347)
  - Wu, K. - Yang (Box 348)
  - Yank - York (Box 349)
  - Yos - Yu (Box 350)
  - Z - Zieg (Box 351)
  - Ziel - Zy (Box 352)
- Student records for Classes of 1978 and earlier, circa 1964-1981; Accession 1983-A-023
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  This accession consists of: 1) folders for students who received the Ph.D. prior to May, 1979, and which had not been included in previous accessions; 2) folders for students who did not receive the Ph.D. (i.e. students who passed the terminal date without completing the Ph.D.,students enrolled in D.S.R. and terminal master"s programs, and students who withdrew from the Graduate School) and whose last registration was in 1971-1972.
  Partial inventory available for boxes 1-51 only.
  - Saharuni, Dora Armenuhi, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Saint-Just, Jacques, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - St.-Maurice, Jean-Pierre, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Sairsingh, Krishna, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Saldivar, Ramon, Jr., 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Salome, Heather Gaye Anderson, 1968-1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Salomon, Marion Kerner, 1968-1974 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Saltman, David Joseph, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Salzman, Phyllis Mali, 1971-1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Sampson, Geoffrey Richard, 1965-1971 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Sandberg, David Karl, 1968-1972 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Sanders, Stephen James, 1972-1977 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Sankus, Patricia Helen, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Santi, Enrico Mario, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Sarabhai, Mana, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Sargent, Alice Brandeis Goldstein, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Sargent, Peter Lindsay, 1965-1972 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Sasao, Noboru, 1873-1977 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Sato, Kenzo, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Satterthwaite, Franklin Bache, Jr., 1966-1975 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Sauder, Gary Wayne, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Saunders, Eleanor Ann, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Saunders, Jon Terry, 1969-1975 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Sayad, João, 1971-1976 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Sayre, Charles Franklin, 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Scaldini, Richard (out slip 4/9/1996)
  - Schaal, Barbara Anna, 1969-1974 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Schade, Richard Erich, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Schafer, Sarah P., 1968 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Schamel, Steven, 1964-1974 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Schank, Joseph David, Jr., 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Schaper, Richard Louis, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Schenkman, Margaret Louise, 1968-1974 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Scherr, David Edward, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Schindler, Walter Leo, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Schiz, Alan Michael
  - Schloss, Christine Harriet Skeeles, 1969-1978 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Schmid, Walter Thomas, 1968-1976 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Schmookler, Andrew Bard, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Schmundt, Maria, 1966-1974 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Schneider, Jan, 1971-1975 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Schneider, Suzanne Beth, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Schoenberg, David Arthur, 1967-1976 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Schoffman, Stuart, 1969-1972 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Schreiber, Carol Joan Tropp, 1973-1977 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Schreiber, Robert Samuel, 1972-1977 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- Student records of students not receiving degrees, 1972-1981; Accession 1983-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
- Student records for the Class of 1979 and students last registered in 1978-1979, Accession 1985-A-008
- Student records for the Class of 1980 and students last registered in 1979-1980, Accession 1987-A-007
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
- Student records for the Classes of 1980-1981 and students last registered in 1980-1981, Accession 1987-A-106
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
- Student records for the Class of 1981-1982 and students last registered in 1982-1983, Accession 1988-A-085
  Restricted Jan 1, 2059
- Student records, Classes of 1982-1983 and students last registered in 1982-1983, Accession 1989-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  Includes folders for students who received Ph.Ds during the period 1982 and 1983 and folders for students who did not receive Ph.Ds but were last registered in 1982 and 1983.
  - Cavallaro, Eduarda (out slip 2/19/1993)
  - Davis, Willliam (out slip 9/22/1989)
  - Dow, David
    General
    See RU 262, accession 2001-A-099, box 3, folder 93.
  - Ducharme, John
    See RU 262, accession 2001-A-099, box 4, folder 176.
  - Escamilla, Robert
    See RU 262, accession 2001-A-099, box 4, folder 178.
  - Marsching, Marjory, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4A)
- Graduate student records, 1967-1980; Accession 19ND-A-440
  - Ex-students, (NO DEGREE)
- Student records, circa 1983-1984; Accession 2001-A-023
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - 1983 Dec
  - 1984 May
- Student records of Ph.D. Recipients, 1984-1986; Accession 2001-A-047
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - 1984 Dec
  - 1985 May
  - 1985 Dec
  - 1986 May
- Student records of Ph.D. Recipients, 1986-1988; Accession 2001-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - 1986 Dec
  - 1987 May
  - 1987 Dec
  - 1988 May
  - 1988 Dec
- Student records of Ph.D. recipients, 1989-1990; Accession 2001-A-074
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - 1989 May
  - 1989 Dec
  - 1990 May
  - 1990 Dec
- Student records of Master's degree recipients, 1979-1992; Accession 2001-A-099
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - 1979 Dec -1980 May
  - 1980 Dec -1981 May
  - 1981 Dec -1982 May
  - 1982 Dec -1983 May
  - 1983 Dec -1984 May
  - 1984 Dec -1985 May
  - 1985 Dec -1986 May
- Student records of Master's degree recipients, 1986-1991; Accession 2001-A-102
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - 1986 Dec -1987 May
    - December 1986-May 1987 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - 1987 Dec -1988 May
  - 1988 Dec -1989 May
  - 1989 Dec - 1990 May
  - 1990 Dec -1991 May
- Student records for Master's and Ph.D. recipients, 1991-1992; Accession 2003-A-028
  - Master's degree recipients, 1991 December - 1992 May
  - Ph.D. recipients, 1991 May
  - Ph.D. recipients, 1991 December
  - Ph.D. recipients, 1992 May
- Student transcripts, circa 1920-1989; Accession 2003-A-161
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065.
  - Frymer, Tikva Simone (Box 4, Folder 4001)
  - Harper, Luby Alexander (Box 5, Folder 5001)
  - Johnson, Norman James (Box 5, Folder 6001)
  - Langston, Thomas Eugene (Box 6, Folder 7001)
  - Matthaei, Julie Ann (Box 7, Folder 8001)
  - Ness, Steven Dale (Box 8, Folder 9001)
  - Rabin, Michael D (Box 9, Folder 10001)
  - Schneider, Gerhart Rudolf (Box 9, Folder 11001)
  - Stewart, Garrett F (Box 10, Folder 12001)
  - Firth, John Luxley (Box 11, Folder 13000)
  - Aiken, William Appleton (Box 13, Folder 14000)
  - Dale, William Sydney Joh (Box 14, Folder 15000)
  - Herrick, Francis Herkomer (Box 15, Folder 16000)
  - McNamara, Mary Florine (Box 16, Folder 17000)
  - Sapelli, Ernest (Box 17, Folder 18000)
  - unspecified (Box 18, Folder 18399)
  - Wray, William Rose (Box 19, Folder 19000)
  - Dickert, Richard Malcolm (Box 21, Folder 20000)
  - Kirk, Stuart Raeburn (Box 22, Folder 21000)
  - Roberts, Achsah Dickinson (Box 23, Folder 22000)
- Student records for Master's and Ph.D. recipients, 1992-1993; Accession 2004-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Ph.D. recipients
  - Ph.D. recipients
  - Masters recipients, 1992-1993
- Student records for Master's degree recipients in teaching, 1950-1970, 1979; Accession 2004-A-098
  - McCarthy, Thomas G. 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 501)
- Student dossier files, circa 1950-1980; Accession 2004-A-154
  - Peterson, Linda K.; English (Box 57, Folder 4001)
  - Stern, Michael; English (Box 71, Folder 5001)
  - Dead Recommendations (Box 84, Folder 5859)
- Student grade lists, circa 1932-1975; Accession 2005-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051
  - Statistics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Statistics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Statistics -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - English -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - English -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - English -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sociology -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sociology -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sociology -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - History -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - History -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - History -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Religious Studies -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Religious Studies -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Religious Studies -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Slavic -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Slavic -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Slavic -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Russian -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - French -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - French -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Italian -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Italian -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Italian -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Portuguese -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Portuguese -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Spanish -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Spanish -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Spanish -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Psychology -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Psychology -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Psychology -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Classics -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Classics -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Classics -Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Law School -A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Law School -B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Undergraduate
    - A Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 40 - 42)
    - B Term, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 43 - 45)
    - A and B Terms, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Full Year, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 47 - 49)
  - Other Schools -1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 50 - 51)
  - Other Schools -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Economics -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Economics -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Economics -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Chemistry -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Chemistry -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Chemistry -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Computer Science -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Computer Science -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Computer Science -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Engineering and Applied Science -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Engineering and Applied Science -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Comparative Literature -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Comparative Literature -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - English -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Religious Studies -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Religious Studies -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Religious Studies -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Sociology -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Sociology -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Sociology -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Forestry and Environmental Science -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Forestry and Environmental Science -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Forestry and Environmental Science -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Undergraduate -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 85 - 88)
  - Undergraduate -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 89 - 92)
  - Undergraduate -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Undergraduate -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Undergraduate -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Other Schools -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Other Schools -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Other Schools -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Spanish -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Spanish -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Statistics -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Statistics -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Statistics -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - French -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - French -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Geology and Geophysics -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Geology and Geophysics -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Geology and Geophysics -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - College Seminars (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Corrected Undergraduate Class Lists 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Corrected HOSAM and Russian Class Lists 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Corrected Classics and History Class Lists 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Institute for Social and Policy Studies -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Institute for Social and Policy Studies -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Institute for Social and Policy Studies -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - French -A and B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - History of Art -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Italian -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Italian -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Italian -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Human Genetics -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Human Genetics -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Human Genetics -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - History of Science and Medicine -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - History of Science and Medicine -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Law School -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Law School -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Linguistics -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Linguistics -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Linguistics -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Mathematics -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Mathematics -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Mathematics -Full Year*/, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - History -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - History -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - History -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Sociology -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Sociology -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Sociology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Statistics -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Statistics -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Statistics -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Undergraduate
    - A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 145 - 146)
    - B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 147 - 149)
    - Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Medical School -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Medical School -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Medical School -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Psychology -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Psychology -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Music -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Music -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Nursing -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Philosophy -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Philosophy -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Philosophy -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Other Schools -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Other Schools -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Pharmacology -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Pharmacology -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Pharmacology -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Microbiology -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Spanish -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Spanish -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Medieval Studies -B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Physics -Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Undergraduate -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Undergraduate -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Undergraduate -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Undergraduate -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Undergraduate -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Undergraduate -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Undergraduate -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Administrative Sciences -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - Administrative Sciences -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Administrative Sciences -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - American Studies -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - American Studies -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - American Studies -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Anatomy -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Anatomy -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Anatomy -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Anthropology -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Anthropology -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Anthropology -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Astronomy -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Astronomy -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Astronomy -Full Year, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - Biology -A Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Biology -B Term, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 201)